现在是宫保鸡丁
And now the kung pao chicken.
很顺利啊
Smooth.
最后
And finally,
我的木须肉
my moo shu pork.
给力!
Whoo-hoo!
菜上齐了  先生们
Oh, there you have it, gentlemen.
整整一桌由机器人上的晚餐
Our entire dinner unpacked by robot.
而且只花了28分钟
And it only took 28 minutes.
是很不错  但我们必须要小心
Impressive, but we must be cautious.
-为什么  -今天机器人来上中国菜
- Why?  - Today, it's a Chinese food retrieval robot.
明天就穿越回过去
Tomorrow, it travels back in time
谋杀莎拉·康纳
and tries to kill Sarah Connor.
我可不觉得这会发生  谢尔顿
I don't think that's going to happen, Sheldon.
确实没发生过
No one ever does.
所以才会发生
That's why it happens.
嘿  晚餐到了吗
Hey. Is the food here?
这是什么
Ooh. What's that?
亲爱的女士
That, dear lady,
这叫沃罗威茨程控手
is the Wolowitz Programmable Hand,
专为维修国际空间站
designed for extravehicular repairs
而设计的延伸臂
on the International Space Station.
好酷啊
Ah, cool.
叫我把酱油递给你
Ask me to pass the soy sauce.
空间站里有人用机械手打酱油吗
Oh, does that come up much on the space station?
通常会是亚裔或犹太航天员
Mostly with Asian and Jewish astronauts.
-好吧  给我酱油  -就来
- All right. Pass the soy sauce.  - Coming up.
工作如何
So how's work?
还不赖吧
Oh, it's not bad.
有点饿了
Kind of hungry.
我们都饿
Yeah, we all are.
等等就好
Just wait.
佩妮  你有想过
You realize, Penny, that the technology
这机械臂所蕴含的科技会在某天
that went into this arm will one day make
让你这种没有能力的服务员下岗么
unskilled food servers such as yourself obsolete.
真的吗
Really?
他们会造往你汉堡上吐口水的机器人吗
They're going to make a robot that spits on your hamburger?
我以为你跟她分手了
I thought you broke up with her.
她为什么在这儿
Why is she here?
好了  搞定
Okay, here we go.
传递酱油
Passing the soy sauce.
手抬起来
Put out your hand.
真不可思议
That's amazing.
我可不会说不可思议
I wouldn't say amazing.
最多不过是比《乡村熊狂欢节》里的
At best, it's a modest leap forward
使用的最基本的科技前进了一小步而已
from the basic technology that gave us Country Bear Jamboree.
嘿  谢尔顿
Hey, Sheldon?
怎么了
Yes?
和平吗
Peace?
不  才不是
No, not peace.
等着
Hang on.
美国航天局知道你用这个作餐巾纸架吗
Does NASA know you're using that thing as a napkin holder?
开玩笑  他们以为这个还在JPL的保险柜里呢
You kidding? They still think it's in a secure locker at JPL.
你偷的
You stole it?
借的
Borrowed.
关键在表现得像把自己的东西带到车上
The trick is to carry it out to your car like you own it.
不好意思
Excuse me.
艾米正在干洗店
Amy's at the dry cleaners,
然后想到一个很有趣的双关语
and she's made a very amusing pun.
"我不喜欢全氯乙烯
"I don't care for perchloroethylene,
不喜欢乙二醇醚"
and I don't like glycol ether."
懂了吗
Get it?
不喜欢乙二醇醚
She doesn't like glycol ether.
听起来就像"亦"
Sounds like "either."
"噗-哈-哈"
"L-O-L."
-艾米是谁  -他女朋友
- Who's Amy?  - His girlfriend.
-谢尔顿有女朋友吗  -她不是我女朋友
- Sheldon has a girlfriend?  - She's not my girlfriend.
-这事儿多久了  -四个月
- How long has this been going on?  - Four months.
她不是我女朋友
She's not my girlfriend.
你是在说  过去的四个月里
Are you telling me, for the past four months
我一直在问你  "有新鲜事吗"
I have been asking you, "What's new?"
你居然从来没想过说
and you never thought to go with,
"谢尔顿有女朋友"吗
"Sheldon has a girlfriend"?
她不是我女朋友
She's not my girlfriend.
啊  等等等等
Ah... d-d-d-d...
他们怎么认识的
How did they meet?
拉杰和我把谢尔顿的信息发到交友网站上
Raj and I entered Sheldon's information on a dating site,
网站速配了艾米·菲拉·福勒
and it spit out Amy Farrah Fowler.
天哪  谢尔顿和艾米
Oh, my God! Sheldon and Amy.
或者像我们所说"谢米"
Or, as we call them, "Shamy."
谢米
Shamy.
我必须好好八一八谢米了
I am so digging the Shamy.
好吧  各单位注意
All right, everyone pay attention.
没错  我是有个朋友叫艾米·菲拉·福勒
Yes, I have a friend named Amy Farrah Fowler.
没错  她是女性
Yes, she is female.
没错  我们每天交流
Yes, we communicate on a daily basis,
但是  她不是我女朋友
but no, she is not my girlfriend.
好吧  那你们交流都说什么
Okay, well, what do you communicate about?
我的物理工作和她的神经生物学工作
Well, my work in physics, her work in neurobiology,
最新话题是论我们生个孩子的可能性
and most recently, the possibility of our having a child together.
<2-23,Penny (spits out drink explosively. Howard types. Robot arm hands Penny a napkin)>谢谢
<2-23,Penny (spits out drink explosively. Howard types. Robot arm hands Penny a napkin)>Thank you.
等等  要孩子
Wait a minute-- a child?
你从没见过这女的
You never see this girl.
只有电邮短信和推特联系
You just e-mail and text and Twitter.
然后现在就考虑要孩子了
Now you're considering having a baby?
艾米指出通过我俩的结合
Amy pointed out that between the two of us,
我们的基因将会有机会
our genetic material has the potential
制造出前所未有的
of producing the first in a line
智力超群  仁慈善良的君主
of intellectually superior, benign overlords
带领人类走向光明未来
to guide humanity to a brighter tomorrow.
我猜想未来的历史学家
I'm guessing that future historians
将会谴责我们不趁这机会杀了谢尔顿
will condemn us for not taking this opportunity to kill Sheldon.
好吧  我有个问题
Okay, I have a question.
请说  佩妮
Yes, Penny.
你不喜欢别人碰你
You don't even like people touching you.
你们怎么做爱呢
How are you going to have sex?
我们干嘛要做爱
Why on earth would we have sex?
亲爱的  你的私处开始发育的时候
Oh, honey, did your mom not have the talk with you?
你妈妈没跟你谈过吗
You know, when your private parts started growing?
我很清楚人类繁殖的方式
I'm quite aware of the way humans usually reproduce,
既脏乱又不卫生
Which is messy, unsanitary,
而且跟你做了三年邻居
And based on living next to you for three years,
听了太多不必要又响亮的呼唤神
Involves loud and unnecessary appeals to a deity.
天呐
Oh, God.
对  就是这句
Yes, exactly.
因此  如果艾米和我
Consequently, if Amy and I choose
选择让一个新生命降临
to bring new life into this world,
我们会让生育专家
It will be accomplished clinically,
在实验室用培养皿受精
with fertility experts in a lab with petri dishes.
这倒提醒我
Which reminds me--
你不仅屁股大  而且头脑简单  精力充沛
you have broad hips and a certain corn-fed vigor.
你的子宫可以代孕吗
Is your womb available for rental?
还想深入八一八谢米恋吗
Still digging the Shamy?
谢尔顿
Look, Sheldon,
先别急着选孕育科
before you race off to the fertility clinic,
你也可以考虑
you might want to think about--
老天  怎么说呢
uh, gee, I don't know--
切实地花点时间陪她
maybe actually spending some time with her.
-你是说约会  -没错
- You mean dating?  - Yeah.
-我不能和艾米约会  -为什么
- I can't date Amy.  - Why not?
她不是我女朋友
She's not my girlfriend.
不要把它当成和女朋友约会
Okay, look, don't think of it as dating a girlfriend.
把它当成
Think of it as, uh...
了解你孩子的未来妈妈
Getting to know the future mother of your child.
我还真没想到
I hadn't considered that.
她将来应该会接触我们的后代
I suppose she will have to have access to our progeny.
你觉得通过短信息
And you don't think I can achieve
我无法达到必要的亲密吗
the required intimacy via text messaging?
应该不能
Probably not.
看来电话公司一直在骗我
It would appear as if the phone companies have been lying to me.
佩妮
Penny.
佩妮  佩妮
Penny. Penny.
你应该知道我站在门的另一边
You do realize I stand on the other side of the door
等你敲完三次门吧
waiting for you to finish knocking three times.
我知道  我能从门缝看到脚的影子
I know. I can see the shadow of your feet under the door.
重点是敲三次很浪费时间
Yeah, my point is it's a waste of time.
如果你想找个
If you're looking for an example
浪费时间的例子
of a waste of time, I would refer you
我们现在的话题就很浪费时间
to the conversation we're having right now.
你有事吗
What do you want?
我决定了接受你的建议
I've decided to take your advice and have arranged
还安排了跟艾米约会
to go on a date with Amy Farrah Fowler.
那太好了
Oh, that's great.
-玩得开心  -等等
- Have fun.  - Wait.
你要载我去
You have to drive me.
-什么  -你知道我不开车
- What?  - You know I don't drive.
-去问莱纳德  -问了
- Well, go ask Leonard.  - I did.
他说  我复述  问问佩妮
He said-- and I quote-- "Ask Penny.
那是她的可笑主意
It was her cockamamy idea."
莱纳德说"可笑"?
Leonard said "cockamamy"?
好吧  那是我说的
Actually, I'm paraphrasing.
在基督教家庭长大
Having been raised in a Christian household,
我实在不习惯他的用语
I'm uncomfortable with the language he used.
老实说
And to be honest,
其实我也不喜欢"可笑"这个词
I'm not entirely comfortable with "cockamamy."
好吧  什么时候约会
Okay, fine. When's the date?
-现在  -现在?
- Now.  - Now?
快点  我们要迟到了
Hurry. We're going to be late.
谢尔顿  你有没有想过
Sheldon, did it ever occur to you
我可能有别的事要忙吗
that I might have other plans?
对不起
I'm sorry.
你有别的事忙吗
Do you have other plans?
倒是没有  不过
Well, no, not per se, but...
这么说这个话题
So this conversation is as pointless
跟你的敲门独白一样没意义咯
as your door-knocking soliloquy?
我去拿我的可笑钥匙
Let me get my... cockamamy keys.
天呐  太爽了
Oh, God, that feels so good.
对  就是那里
Yeah, that's the spot.
宝贝儿
Oh, baby.
霍华德  吃饭啦
Howard, dinner's ready!
我一会再吃
I'll eat later.
现在很忙
I'm busy!
爽啊
Oh, yeah.
就跟人手一样
Just like a real hand.
谢谢你载我去
Thank you for driving me.
不客气
You're welcome.
但我希望你不穿人字拖
I wish you weren't wearing flip-flops.
穿人字拖开车很危险
It's dangerous to drive in flip-flops.
-谢尔顿  -对不起
- Sheldon.  - Sorry.
我只是不想成为另一个人字拖的受害者
I just don't want to be yet another flip-flop fatality.
我能问个问题吗
Can I ask you a question?
鉴于你的社区大学学历
Given your community college education,
我鼓励你尽量多问
I encourage you to ask me as many as possible.
好  我的问题是
Yeah. Well, my question is--
其实我很清楚答案
and I'm pretty sure I know the answer--
这是你第一次约会吗
Is this your first date?
那得看情况
That depends.
跟我妹在国庆日
Does square-dancing with my sister
青年敬耶稣方块舞会上
at a Teens for Jesus Fourth of July Hoedown
跳舞算吗
count as a date?
不算
No.
那这是我第一次约会
Then, this is my first date.
那有几件事
Okay. Well, then, there's a couple of things
你应该要知道
you should probably know.
我有一个硕士学位和两个博士学位
I have a master's degree and two doctorates.
我应该知道的事  我都知道
The things I should know, I do know.
我的意思是  我比你更清楚约会
My point is, I know more about dating than you,
而且如果你真有你认为的那么聪明
and if you were as smart as you think you are,
你就会听我的话
you would listen to me.
如果你是约会专家  那怎么我今晚有约会
If you know so much, how come I have a date tonight
而你只能当我的司机呢
and you have nothing better to do than drive me to it?
说得好
Fair point.
《水行侠》的有些问题我想不明白
You know, there's something I've always wondered about Aquaman.
-什么  -他去哪便便
- Yeah?  - Where does he poop?
什么
What?
亚特兰蒂斯的马桶长什么样
What would a toilet look like in Atlantis?
你怎么冲掉呢
How would you flush it?
就算你冲掉了  便便又能冲去哪呢
And when you did flush it, where would the poop go?
一会儿再讨论
Hold that thought.
喂  霍华德  怎么了
Hey, Howard. What's going on?
啥
What...
等等  霍华德  慢点说
Hold on. Howard, Howard, slow down.
机械手卡在你的什么上了
The robot hand is stuck on your what?
说出来肯定吓你一跳
You're not going to believe this.
艾米  听谢尔顿说
So, um, Amy, Sheldon tells me
你是一个神经...什么来着
you're a neuro... something-or-other.
是神经生物学家
Neurobiologist.
你车的"检查引擎"灯亮了
Your "check engine" light is on.
噢  不管它
Yeah, it's okay.
但如果灯亮了就说明...
But the light indicates...
不用费心了
Don't bother.
我已经浪费太多时间
I've wasted many an hour
攻击这座顽固的风车了
tilting at that particular windmill.
你用的什么香水吗
Uh, what is that scent you're wearing?
真好闻
It smells great.
去屑洗发水
Dandruff shampoo.
我头皮干燥
I have dry scalp.
你发质看着很好呀
Well, your hair looks very nice.
你是同性恋么
Are you a homosexual?
当然不  我只是赞美你而已
No, no, I'm just giving you a compliment.
要你是同性恋  赞美不听着更由衷吗
Would have been more flattered if you were a homosexual.
那啥  来点音乐怎样
Guys, how 'bout some music?
哦不  我可不想要
Oh, no, I wouldn't care for that.
艾米  你呢
Amy?
我也是  谢了
No, thank you.
好吧
Okay.
那就诡异地沉默着吧
Uncomfortable silence it is.
谢尔顿  你有没有告诉艾米
Hey, Sheldon, have you told Amy
你小时候在德州长大的经历
what it was like for you growing up in Texas?
没有
No.
哎  为什么不告诉她
Well, why don't you tell her?
好吧
All right.
痛苦得要死
It was hell.
艾米  有什么想法么
Any follow up, Amy?
没有
No.
我在内布拉斯加州长大
I myself grew up in Nebraska.
奥马哈郊外的一个小镇
Small town outside of Omaha.
很好的地方  大多是家庭农场  还有些制毒窝点
Nice place, mostly family farms, a few meth labs.
不好意思  这样还不如诡异地沉默呢
I'm sorry, how is this better than uncomfortable silence?
我也不知道  不过是试着找点话题
I don't know. I was just trying something.
麻瓜一个[此处引用《哈利波特》里的说法]
Muggles.
你是滑倒摔进机械手里的吗
You slipped and fell into a robot hand?
对
Yes.
鸡鸡先着地
Penis first?
对  快帮我
Yes. Now, help me!
我本来想建议用润滑剂
I'd suggest a lubricant, but I have a feeling
但我想其实你已经栽在润滑剂里了
you fell on some of that as well.
不好笑  莱纳德
Not funny, Leonard.
是吗  一个机械手卡在你小弟弟上
Really? A robot hand's got a death grip on your junk, dude.
这还不好笑吗  不信你问别人
That's funny, ask anyone.
拜托  趁我妈还没进来  快把这玩意弄掉
Plea-- before my mother walks in, get this off me!
唔  我看看
Okay, let's see.
别  别碰电脑
No, no! Don't touch.
程序暂停了
The program is paused.
那就重新启动呗
Well, then let's un-pause it.
别  导入错误的程序
No, no! I loaded the wrong program.
这玩意以为自己在外太空握着把螺丝刀呢
The hand thinks it's holding a screwdriver in outer space.
要是程序继续  它就要开始扭了
If you continue the program, it's gonna start twisting.
好吧
A-All right.
这样如何
Um, how about this.
小熊维尼的脑袋卡在蜂蜜树上时
When-when Winnie the Pooh got his head stuck
他的伙伴们就会上去拉住他
in the honey tree, his friends all grabbed onto him
然后往外拔啊拔啊拔
and pulled and pulled.
你爱咋咋地
You do what you want,
我可不想碰其他男人的"蜂蜜树"
I'm not touching another man's honey tree.
好吧  不拔了
All right, uh, forget pulling.
那就找把电锯  直接锯掉
How about we get an electric saw and cut it off?
啥  不准用电锯
What?! No saws!
一个包皮环切还不够吗
One circumcision was enough.
那乙快焊炬呢
How about an acetylene torch?
好吧  不敢相信我还要声明这些
Okay, I can't believe this needs to be said out loud.
不准拔  不准用电锯和焊炬
No pulling, no saws, no torches.
那你要我们做啥
Well, then what do you want us to do?
霍华德  我做了饼干
Howard, I made cookies for you
给你和你的小伙伴
and your little friends!
好极了  老妈  多谢
That's great, Mom, thanks!
我送上来  再带点夏威夷宾治酒
I'll bring them up with some Hawaiian Punch!
别上来
Don't come up here!
干嘛  看不起你妈吗
Why not?! Are you ashamed of your mother?!
话是没错  但这不是关键
Yes, but that's not the point!
快帮帮忙
Get me out of here.
你有想法吗  拉杰
You have any ideas, Raj?
现在啊  我满脑子都是饼干和夏威夷宾治酒
Right now, all I can think about is cookies and Hawaiian Punch.
好吧  换个话题
Hey, here's another possible topic of conversation.
今晚是谢尔顿的盛大之夜啊
This is a big night for Sheldon.
是吧  谢尔顿
Right, Sheldon?
盛大
Big night?
冬至日的夜晚才叫大
The winter solstice is a big night.
在南加利福尼亚
It's over 14 hours
一共有整整14小时呢
in Southern California.
这句话仿得真有意思
That's an amusing factoid.
谢谢
Thank you.
不
No, no.
我是说  今晚是谢尔顿第一次正式约会
My point is, uh, tonight is Sheldon's first official date.
你们继续吧
Discuss.
真的吗
Is this true?
当然  在国庆日上的青年敬基督
Apparently, a semi-incestuous Teens for Jesus
方块舞会上的那次半乱伦约会不算
Fourth of July Hoedown didn't count.
艾米  那你呢
So, um, Amy, what about you?
你约会过吗
Do you date much?
一年一次
Once a year.
我和我妈说好了
It's a deal I made with my mother
这样她就不唠叨这事
in exchange for her silence on the matter,
还可以偶尔用她的乔治·富曼烤架
as well as the occasional use of her George Foreman Grill
锁住美味  没有脂肪
that seals in the flavor without the fat.
你呢  佩妮
How about you, Penny?
你约会过很多次吗
Do you go on many dates?
其实也没有很多次啦
Uh, yeah, I wouldn't say many.
有几个吧
A few.
这算啥表情
What's...?
你把约171个不同男人描述为"有几个"
Your characterization of approximately 171 different men as "A few."
什么
What...
你怎么算的171个
Where did you get 171 men?
简单的推断
Simple extrapolation.
我认识你的这三年来
In the three years that I've known you,
你有两年是单身
you were single for two.
在那两年里  你跟17名追求者约会过
During that time, I saw 17 different suitors.
往前倒推的话  请纠正如果观察有误
If we work backwards, correcting for observation bias
并假设你初次约会年龄为15岁
and postulate an initial dating age of 15
等等  等等
Whoa, wait, wait, wait.
我才不是15岁开始约会的
I did not start dating at 15.
抱歉  十六岁
I'm sorry. Sixteen?
十四
Fourteen.
我的错
My mistake.
假设钟形曲线的左半部分在目前达到峰值
Now, assuming the left side of a bell curve peaking around the present,
那就是说总数为193人
that would bring the total up to 193 men.
正负8人
Plus or minus eight men.
太厉害了
Remarkable.
你跟这些人都有过性关系吗
Did you have sexual intercourse with all of these men?
没有
No.
这个数字要算的话也相当简单
Although that number would be fairly easy to calculate.
基于我早上在她公寓门口尴尬邂逅
Based on the number of awkward encounters I've had
陌生过夜男士的数量
with strange men leaving her apartment in the morning,
加上遇见她穿着前晚衣服
plus the number of times she's returned home wearing the same clothes
早上回家的次数
she wore the night before...
好了  谢尔顿  我们都明白你意思了
Okay, Sheldon, I think you've made your point.
那就是193人
So we multiply 193--
减去她失去童贞之前的21人
minus 21 men before the loss of virginity--
即172人乘以0.18
so 172 times 0.18 gives us...
30.96位性伴侣
30.96 sexual partners.
约等于31
Let's round that up to 31.
好了  谢尔顿  这根本不对
Okay, Sheldon, you are so wrong.
跟实际数字大相径庭
That is not even close to the real number.
这里给我来杯酒
I'm gonna need a drink over here.
这真有趣
This is very interesting.
个人的文化认知是非常主观的
Cultural perceptions are subjective.
佩妮  在你看来  你是荡妇吗
Penny, to your mind, are you a slut?
不  不是
No! No!
不是
No.
我们还是自顾自用餐好了  好吗
Let's just all finish our dinners, okay?
确实是个有趣的话题
This is an interesting topic.
你有多少次性经验
How many sexual encounters have you had?
这要看志愿参加科学实验
Does volunteering for a scientific experiment
通过电子系统刺激人脑中的
in which orgasm was achieved by electronically
愉悦中心区获得性高潮也算吗
stimulating the pleasure centers of the brain count?
我想应该算的
I should think so.
那就是128次
Then 128.
好的  进来吧
Okay, come on.
就快到了
Almost there.
-别用力拉  -我没在拉
- Don't tug. - No tugging.
下回你自己搞定
Next time, take your own advice.
打扰下  能否帮帮我们
Excuse me, could you help us out?
天哪天哪天哪
My, my, my.
这怎么回事
What do we have here?
我不小心滑倒了
I slipped and fell.
嗯  这我们经常碰到
Yeah, we get that a lot.
这是什么
What is this?
是机器人的手臂
It's a robot arm.
那机器人的其他部分呢
Where's the rest of the robot?
我就造了手臂
I only built the arm.
因为你就需要这个  是吗
'Cause that's all you needed, right?
能先帮我解决这再说吗
Can you please just help me?!
好吧  好吧
All right, all right.
稍安勿躁
Hang on, stay calm.
请派护理员送轮椅来
I need an orderly with a wheelchair.
有被机械手钳住小弟弟的来看急诊
I got a robot hand grasping a man's penis out here.
你讲话就不能含蓄点
You think you could be a little more discreet?
抱歉  "机械手钳住小弟弟"这种情况未设代码
I'm sorry,we don't have a code for "Robot hand grasping a man's penis."
它为何还连到电脑上
Why is it hooked up to a computer?
-就是通过电脑控制机械手的  -但电脑死机了
- Uh, it's what controls the arm. - But it's frozen.
你试过关机重启吗
Did you try turning it off and back on again?
不  这事远比这复杂得多
No, you see, it's more complicated than that.
别  住手
No, wait!
小熊维尼终于从蜂蜜树中脱困
Winnie the Pooh is out of the honey tree.
现在能让我们吃饼干和夏威夷宾治了吧
Now can we have cookies and Hawaiian Punch?
你说得对
You were right.
这个夜晚确实收获颇丰
This was a very productive evening.
今晚我见识到了艾米·菲拉·福勒全新的一面
I saw a whole new side of Amy Farrah Fowler tonight.
我没跟31个男人有过性关系
I did not have sex with 31 guys.
我很乐意验算下  但数字不会骗人的
I'll be happy to check the math, but numbers don't lie, Penny.
不管怎样  现在我和艾米已共度了"美好时光"
In any event, now that Amy and I have spent quality time together,
我就更有信心
I feel much more confident
继续将我俩关系发展到下一阶段了
proceeding to the next stage of our relationship.
什么阶段
And that is?
利用试管授精和代孕
Using in vitro fertilization and a surrogate uterus
生下我们的后代向人类献礼
to gift humanity with our progeny.
你还在计划这个
You're still on that?
人世无常  人类难道不该有所安慰
In these uncertain times, doesn't humanity deserve a gift?
好吧  这样吧
Okay, you know what?
我再换种方式跟你说
I'm gonna come at this in a whole new way.
谢尔顿  如果你想用培养皿造出你跟艾米的孩子
Sheldon, if you try to make a baby with Amy in a petri dish,
我一定会去告诉你的妈妈
I'm gonna tell your mother on you.
这威胁不了我
That's no threat.
我妈一直都想抱孙子的
My mother's always wanted a grandchild.
真的  你那虔信基督再生的母亲
Really? Your deeply religious born-again Christian mother
会想要一个非婚生的试管婴儿当她的孙子
wants a test-tube grandbaby born out of wedlock?
诅咒你
Curses.
我要是早点想出这招
If I'd thought of that in the first place,
今晚也不用受这份罪了
I could've saved myself this whole night.
现在还不算晚
Well, it's not that late.
你还是可以出去寻找32号性伴侣
You could still go out and look for number 32.
晚安
Good night.
霍华德  怎么了
Hey, Howard, what's up?
我决定不要孩子了
I've decided not to procreate.
好的  很好
Yeah, yeah, great.
霍华德  慢点说
Howard, uh, slow down.
什么叫悲剧重演了
What do you mean it happened again?